BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 18) 6178/018
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 18)
1972- 2011
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United States Department of Labor
Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS)
6178/018
91 cubic feet
91 linear ft.
Collective labor agreements.
7256644
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, October 09, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 21, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6178/001: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 1) 6178/002: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 2) 6178/003: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 3) 6178/004: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 4) 6178/006: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 6) 6178/007: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 7) 6178/008: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 8) 6178/009: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 9) 6178/010: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 10) 6178/011: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 11) 6178/012: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 12) 6178/013: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 13) 6178/014: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 14) 6178/015: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 15) 6178/016: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 16) 6178/017: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 17) 6178/019: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 19) 6178/020: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 20) 6178/021(d): BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 21) Digital 6178/022 mf: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 22) on Microfilm 6178/023: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 23)
Industrial relations -- United States; Collective bargaining -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- Paper industry -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- Building trades -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- Iron and steel workers -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- Teachers -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- Nurses -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- Service industries -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- Automobile industry and trade -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- Communication and traffic -- United States; United States.; United States. Dept. of Labor--Archives; United States. Bureau of Labor Statistics--Archives
7256644
- Code 4: Allied-Signal Inc., Kansas City Division and District Lodge No. 71 International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1990- 1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  October 15, 1990 - October10, 1999
- Code 4: Honeywell International Inc., Federal Manufacturing and Technologies and Atomic Energy Lodge No. 314, 1999-2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  was lodge 71
- Code 4: Bendix Kansas City Division and District Lodge No. 71 of the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1972- 1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- UAW and the Guide Corporation, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  March 16, 2000
- Code 6: Verizon Delaware Inc. and Communication Workers of America, 2000-2003 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Code 7: Verizon Delaware Inc. and Communication Workers of America, 2000-2003 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Diamond State Telephone Commercial Union CWA - Local 13100
- Code 7: General Dynamics Convair Division and the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1984-1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Code 8: Raytheon Missile Systems and the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1999-2006 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  10/25/99-10/27/03 and 11/2/03-11/5/06
- Code 8: Hughes Aircraft Company and the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1981-1987 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Code 9: Lockheed Martin Missiles and Space and the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Code 9: Lockheed Missiles and Space Company, Inc. and the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1980- 1986 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Code 10: UAW and Its Locals No. 738, No. 766, and No. 788, 1993-1999 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Code 11: Guide Corporation and Local 663 UAW, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Code 13: Local Union 328 United Food and Commercial Workers and The Stop and Shop Supermarket Company, 1999-2001 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Code 14: Midwest Generation EME, LLC and Local Union 15 of the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1999-2001 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  December 15, 1999- March 31, 2001
- Code 17: Remington Arms Company, Inc. Ilion Plant, 1991-1997 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Code 17: Remington Arms Company, Inc. Ilion, New York and Employees' Mutual Association of Ilion, Inc., 1977-1988 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Code 18: Olin Corporation and the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1989-2000 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  12/1/1989-12/1/1992 and 12/7/1992-12/3/1995 and 12/4/1995-12/3/2000
- Code 18: Olin Corporation and the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1971-1989 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Code 20: United Steelworkers of America, Local Union 8031, 1987-2002 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Code 22: UAW Local Union 848, 1988-2000 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Code 202: Chicago Midwest Meat Association and United Food and Commercial Workers Union Local 100A, 1991-2003 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  11/1/91-10/31/94; 11/1/94-10/31/97; 11/1/2000-10/31/2003
- Code 206: Bakery, Confectionery and Tobacco Workers' International Union, 1996-2000 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  6/96- 10/2000
- Code 207: Hormel Foods Corporation and UFCW/AFL-CIO Local #9, 1973-2003 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Code 210: AFL-CIO United Food and Commercial Workers' International Union and the Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, 1970-2002 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Code 211: United Food and Commercial Workers' International Union, 1986-2004 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Code 215: UFCW Butchers, Food Handlers, and Allied Workers Union of Greater New York and New Jersey- Local No. 174, 1971-1999 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Code 228: International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1974-2004 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Code 243: International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local No. 22, 28, 61, 509, 549, 592, 822, 1993-1999 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Code 254: Teamsters Local 228, 1997-2003 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Code 270: American Federation of Grain Millers, 1984-2003 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Code 282: Local Union 300 of the Bakery, Confectionery, and Tobacco Workers' International Union, 1996-2004 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Code 286: Local 3 of the Bakery, Confectionery, and Tobacco Workers International Union, 1993-2003 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Code 291: American Crystal Sugar Company and the American Federation of Grain Millers, 1987-2002 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Code 298: Michigan Sugar Company and the American Federation of Grain Millers, 1971-2004 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Code 303: Hershey Chocolate Company and Local Union 464 of the Bakery, Confectionery, and Tobacco Workers' International Union, 1961- 2005 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Code 323: Winery Employees Association and the United Food and Commercial Workers International Union- Locals 45 and 186, 1971- 1999 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Code 332: Campbell Soup Company and the United Food and Commercial Workers International Union- Locals 911 and 186, 1987- 2004 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Code 365: International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1974-2004 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Code 369: Campbell Soup Company and Local No. 540 of the U.F.& C.W.I.U, 1995-2001 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Code 375: U.F. & C.W.I.U Local No. 38, 1972-2005 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Code 378: Chauffeurs, Teamsters, and Helpers Local 822, 1976-2002 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Code 384: U.F. & C.W.I.U. Local 222, 1970-2009 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Code 385: Teamsters Local 738, 1983-1998 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Code 400: Bryan Foods, Inc. and the U.F. & C.W.I.U, 1987-2004 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Code 402: I.B.T. Local 173, 1975-2001 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Code 405: J.R. Simplot Company and the Teamster Food Processors, Drivers, Warehousemen and Helpers Local 670, 1978-2004 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Code 417: Delta Pride Catfish, Inc. and UFCW Local 1529, 1987-2004 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Code 420: UFCW Local 1529, 1991-2005 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Code 422: Teamsters California State Council, 1991-2000 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Code 423: IBP, Inc. and U.F. & C.W.I.U Local 431, 1990-2002 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Code 444: U.F.C.W. Local 227, 1996-2003 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Code 445: U.F.C.W. Local 227, 1994-2006 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Code 506: Lorillard Tobacco Company and Local 317 of the Bakery, Confectionery, and Tobacco Workers International Union, 1971- 2003 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Code 508: Philip Morris U.S.A and the Bakery, Confectionery, and Tobacco Workers International Union, 1992-2002 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Code 513: Brown and Williamson Tobacco Company and Local 362-T of the B.C.T.W.I.U, 1984-1999 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Code 515: Philip Morris USA and Lodge #10 of the I.A.M.A.W., 1992-2002 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Code 602: Dan River Inc. and Local 248 of the United Textile Workers of America, 1980-1997 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc., 1993-2000 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Code 800: Clothing Manufacturers Association of the United States of America, 1974-1990 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  1 of 2
- Code 800: Clothing Manufacturers Association the United States of America, 1995-2004 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  2 of 2
- Code 824: Clothing Manufacturers Collective Agreements, 1970-1997 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  includes the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; the American Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Association; the New York Coat and Suit Association; the Infants', Children's, and Girl's Sportswear and Coat Association; the New York Coat, Suit, Dress, Rainwear and Allied Worker's Union; and the Joint Board of Coat, Suit, and Allied Garment Workers' Unions
- Code 828: New York Skirt and Sportswear Association, Inc., 1997-2001 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  6/1/1997-5/31/2001
- Code 857: Plastic Soft Materials Manufacturers' Association, Inc., 1972-1998 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Code 858, 1994-2001 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Code 860: International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1970-2003 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Code 861: United Textile Workers of America Local 211, 1973-1999 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Code 867: Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees and Levi Strauss & Co., 1997-2000 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Code 876: Greater Blouse, Skirt, and Undergarment Association, Inc.(Sportswear Division) and Amalgamated Ladies' Garment Cutters' Union Local 10, 2001-2004 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  6/2001-6/2004
- Associated General Contractors, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Code 1010: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 2000-2007 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  3/2000-3/2004 and 3/2004-12/2007
- Code 1011: Chicago and Northeast Illinois District Council of Carpenters, 1984-2007 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Code 1028: Weyerhaeuser Company and the International Woodworkers of America, 1982-2003 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Code 1031: Western Council of Industrial Workers, 1992-2004 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Code 1131: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1993-2007 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Code 1033: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1993-1998 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Code 1200: Consolidated Papers, Inc., 1987-1999 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Code 1200: Consolidated Papers, Inc. and the United Paperworkers International Union, 1972-1990 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Code 1217: Kimberly-Clark Corporation and the United Paperworkers International Union, 1972-2000 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Code 1221: Mead Paper Chillicothe Mill and the United Paperworkers International Union, 1978-1988 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Code 1221: Mead Paper Chilllicothe Mill and the United Paperworkers International Union, 1988-2000 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Code 1225: United Paperworkers International Local 900, 1972-2001 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Code 1226: Longview Fibre Company and the Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers, 1973-2000 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Code 1226: Longview Fibre Company and the Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers, 1984-1990 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Code 1233: Westvaco Corporation and the United Paperworkers International Union, 1980-2001 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Code 1245: United Paperworkers International Union and the International Union of Operating Engineers, 1983-2003 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Code 1257: United Paperworkes International Union, the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, and Bowater Southern Paper Co., 1984-2008 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Code 1226: United Paperworkers International Union and Georgia-Pacific Corporation Crossett Division, 1971-2000 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Code 1268: United Paperworkers International Union Nos. 950, 952, and 966 and the James River Corporation, 1983-2001 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Code 1271: Procter and Gamble Paper Products Company and the United Paperworkers International Union, 1983-2001 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Code 1272: Champion International Corporation and the United Paperworkers International Union, 1987-1998 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Code 1275: Weyerhaeuser Paper Company, the United Paperworkers International Union, and the International Union of Operating Engineers, 1986-2002 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  U.P.I.U. Nos 1356 and 1423; I.U.O.E No .415
- Code 1281: Union Camp Corporation, the United Paperworkers International Union, and the International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, 1982-1994 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  U.P.I.U Nos 1488 and 505; I.B.F.O No. 176
- Code 1282: Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers No. 5, 1981-1999 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Code 1284: Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Locals 183-644, 1981-2005 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Code 1285: Scott Paper Company and the United Paperworkers International Union No. 448, 1984-1998 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Code 1293: Federal Paper Board Company and Local 738 of the United Paperworkers International Union, 1986-2000 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Code 1304: Champion International and Locals 193, 1137, and 1161 of the United Paperworkers International Union, 1990-1995 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Code 1404: The New York Times and the Newspaper Guild of New York, 1987-2000 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Code 1411: Chicago Lithographers Association and Chicago Local 458-3M G.C.U., 1991-2007 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Code 1419: The Metropolitan Lithographers Association and Local 1 Amalgamated Lithographers of America, 1973-2001 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Code 1415: The Washington Post and the Washington-Baltimore Newspaper Guild Local 32035, 1995-2002 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Code 1454: Dow Jones & Co., Inc. and The Independent Association of Publishers' Employees, 1996-2002 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  CWA Local 1096
- Code1457: Northern California Newspaper Guild Local 52 and the San Francisco Newspaper Publishers Association, 1983-1998 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Code 1458: Aluminum, Brick, and Glass Workers International Union Local 299, 1991-2001 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Code 1459: National Sample Card Manufacturers Association Inc. and the United Paperworkers International Union Local 413, 1990- 2001 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Code 1475: Philadelphia Newspapers, Inc. and The Newspaper Guild of Greater Philadelphia Local 10, 1995-2000 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Code 1476: The Boston Globe and BGEA/TNG Local 31245, 1997-2000 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Code 1480: BellSouth and Communications Workers of America, 1998-2001 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Code 1604: Chemical Workers Association and the E.I. Du Pont de Nemours & Company, 1970-1978 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Code 1608: Hanford Atomic Metal Trades Council and Fluor Daniel Hanford, Inc., 1997-2002 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Code 1631: Industrial and Allied Workers Local Union 101, the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America, and the Chesterfield Plant, 1999-2005 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Code 1633: Seaford Nylon Employees Council, Inc. and E.I. Du Pont de Nemours and Company, 1974-1994 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Code 1634: United Workers, Inc. and E.I. Du Pont de Nemours and Company, 1973-1989 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Code 1643: International Chemical Workers Union Local 143 and the American Cyanamid Company, 1973-2008 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Code 1643: International Chemical Workers Union Local 143 and the American Cyanamid Company, 1976-1996 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Code 1644: Merck, the International Union of Operating Engineers, and the Paper, Allied-Industrial, Chemical, and Energy Workers International Union, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Code 1644: Merck and the Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union, 1981-1997 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  Locals 8-86, 8-580, 8-575; 2 of 2
- Code 1645: Merck and Co., Inc. and the Paper, Allied-Industrial, Chemical and Energy Workers International Local 2-86, 2001- 2004 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Code 1645: Merck & Co, Inc. and the Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union Local 8-86, 1973-1998 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Code 1682: International Union of Operating Engineers and the Dow Chemical Company, 1996-1999 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  Local 564
- Code 1683: International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers and PPG Industries, Inc., 1993-2003 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  Local 470
- Code 1828: Gulf Coast Industrial Workers Union and Exxon Company, USA, 1994-1998 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Code 1903: United Steelworkers of America and Bridgestone/Firestone, Inc., 1991-2001 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  1 of 3
- Code 1903: Firestone, Inc. and the International Union of the United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, 1985- 1996 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  2 of 3
- Code 1903: Firestone/URW, 1988-1991 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  3 of 3
- Code 1904: General Motors Corporation, 1987-2002 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Code 1906: B.F. Goodrich Company and the U.R.C.L.P.W.A., 1973-1985 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Code 1906: Uniroyal Goodrich Tire Manufacturing and the United Steelworkers of America, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  June 12, 1997; Local Union No. 753; 2 of 3
- 1906: Uniroyal Goodrich Tire Manufacturing, 1988-2000 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  United Steelworkers of America and the U.R.C.L.P.W.A.; 3 of 3
- Code 1908: Goodyear Tire and Rubber Company and the U.R.C.L.P.W.A, 1994-1997 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Code 1908: Goodyear Tire and Rubber Company and the United Steelworkers of America, 2000-2003 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  Local Union 915; 2 of 2
- Code 1908: Goodyear Dunlop Tires North America, LTD and the United Steelworkers of America, 1997-2003 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  Local Union 135; 2 of 2
- Code 1910: Cooper Tire and Rubber Company, 1994-2000 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  United Steel Workers of America and the U.R.C.L.P.W.A. Local Unions 207 and 752
- Code 1911: Cooper Tire and Rubber Company and the United Steelworkers of America, 1996-2002 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  Local Union 752
- Code 1913: Goodyear Dunlop Tires, United Steelworkers of America, and the U.R.C.L.P.W.A, 1994-2000 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  Local Union 915 and 135
- Code 1914: United Steelworkers of America and Continental General Tire, Inc., 2000 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  November 29, 2000; Local 850
- Code 1926: UNITE Local Union #132-98-102, 1982-2004 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Code 1927: Glass, Molders, Pottery, Plastics, and Allied Workers International Union, 1986-2005 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Code 1935: Rubbermaid Incorporated and the United Steelworkers of America, 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  November 8, 1996 and September 30, 1997; Local Union 302L
- Code 1934: Kelly-Springfield Tire Company, U.R.C.L.P.W.A./ United Steelworkers of America, 1979-1997 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  Local 746
- Code 1936: General Tire and URW, 1982-1997 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  Local 665
- Code 1938: Kelly-Springfield Tire Company/ URW/United Steelworkers of America, 1984-1996 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  Local 959
- Code 1939: Kelly-Springfield Tire Company/URW/United Steelworkers of America, 1985-1998 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  Local 745
- Code 2303: Anchor Hocking Glass Company/American Flint Glass Workers Union, 1971-2005 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Code 2308: Corning Glass Works/American Flint Glass Workers Union, 1971-1999 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Code 2313: American Flint Glass Workers Union/Glass Container Industrial Relations Council, 1990-2005 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Code 2339: Owens-Corning Fiberglas Corporation, 1972-2004 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Code 2350: Glass, Molders, Pottery, Plastics, and Allied Workers International Union, 1990-2005 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Code 2351: Glass, Molders, Pottery, Plastics, and Allied Workers International Union, 1990-2002 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Code 2352: Glass, Molders, Pottery, Plastics, and Allied Workers International Union, 1977-2005 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  Anchor Glass Container Corporation and Latchford Glass Company
- Code 2355: Glass, Molders, Pottery, Plastics, and Allied Workers International Union, 1983-2002 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Code 2357: Glass, Molders, Pottery, Plastics, and Allied Workers International Union, 1972-2002 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Code 2359: Glass, Molders, Pottery, Plastics and Allied Workers International Union, 1980-1993 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Code 2361: Glass, Molders, Pottery, Plastics and Allied Workers International Union/Owens-Brockway Glass Container Inc., 1989- 2005 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Code 2362: Owens-Illinois Inc./Glass Bottle Blowers Association, 1971-1988 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Code 2363: Glass, Molders, Pottery, Plastics and Allied Workers International Union/Owens-Brockway Glass Container Inc., 1993- 2005 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Code 2368: Glass, Molders, Pottery, Plastics and Allied Workers International Union, 1974-2005 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Code 2453: Teamsters Local Union No. 86, 1992-2002 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Code 2500: ACME Steel Company/United Steelworkers of America, 1989-2000 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Code 2502: Allegheny Ludlum Steel/United Steelworkers of America, 1990-2002 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Code 2504: Armco Employees Independent Federation Inc., 1983-1999 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Code 2504: AK Steel Corporation/Armco Employees Independent Federation Inc., 1994-2000 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Code 2505: Armco Inc./Butler Armco Independent Union, 1983-1996 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Code 2506: Armco/United Steelworkers of America, 1983-2000 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Code 2509: United Steelworkers of America Local No. 1940, 1984-2002 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Code 2524: United Steelworkers of America/ISPAT Inland Inc., 1989-1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Code 2529: Independent Steel Workers' Alliance/Keystone Steel and Wire, 1993-1996 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Code 2531: USW No. 4134/Lone Star Steel Company, 1980-2005 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Code 2532: United Steelworkers of America, 1983-2008 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Code 2534: Independent Steelworkers Union/Weirton Steel Corporation, 1977-1996 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Code 2544: USW/United States Steel (USX Corporation), 1991-2008 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Code 2544: USW/United States Steel (USX Corporation), 1999-2004 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  8/1/1999-8/1/2004; 2 of 2
- Code 2545: USW/United States Steel (USX Corporation), 1987-2008 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Code 2551: USW/Wheeling-Pittsburg Steel Corporation, 1983-2002 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Code 2555: USW/American Steel Foundries, 1986-2004 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Code 2563: USWA/Tyler Pipe Company, 1993-2005 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  Local No. 1157
- Code 2589: USWA/ASARCO Inc., 1995-2004 (Box 16, Folder 4)